Guide to the Samuel P. Hays Post-World War II Radical Movements Publications Collection, 1915-1982 AIS.1981.18
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Samuel P. Hays Post-World War II Radical Movements Publications Collection
1915-1982
1960-1976
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Hays, Samuel P.
AIS.1981.18
170 Linear Feet (136 boxes)
Created by Dr. Samuel P. Hays, a professor of history at the University of Pittsburgh, this collection consists of publications produced by organizations and individuals from both the radical right and radical left of the political spectrum. It includes pamphlets and various types of periodicals such as journals, magazines, newsletters and newspapers, as well as some informational materials on the organizations that published them.
Arrangement
The collection is organized as it was when received from Dr. Hays, who divided it into seven categories and then arranged the materials alphabetically.
Series I. Religious Periodicals
Series II. Underground Newspapers
Series III. Radical Right Publications
Series IV. Radical Left Publications
Series V. Pamphlets
Series VI. Organizations and Individuals
Series VII. Subject Files
Biography
Dr. Samuel P. Hays was a professor in the University of Pittsburgh's Department of History from 1960, when he accepted the position of chairman of that department, until 1973. He then became Distinguished Service Professor of History from 1973 until his retirement in 1991. Dr. Hays received his Bachelor of Arts degree from Swarthmore College in 1948 and both his Master of Arts (1949) and Doctor of Philosophy (1953) degrees from Harvard University. At Harvard, he held a Theodore Roosevelt Memorial Fellowship. Before coming to Pitt, Dr. Hays taught at the University of Illinois (1952-1953) and the University of Iowa (1953-1960).
Dr. Hays was involved in many professional activities, including being vice president and a member of the executive committee of the Society for Environmental History. He has published 10 books, over 25 book chapters, and nearly 40 journal articles, one of which was based on the student strike at Columbia University (1968), in which he charted both left and right student groups and outlined their similar roles on opposite ends of the political spectrum.
Influenced by history colleagues while at the University of Iowa, Dr. Hays witnessed the creation of a "tensions" collection developed by Dr. Ralph Ellsworth, that is, material created by interest groups to further their cause, but was not being actively collected by libraries. Dr. Hays took this idea with him to Pitt and "decided to emphasize the radical fringes of the political spectrum with the idea that they represented different poles of the political spectrum but, in fact, were much alike." He kept this interest alive until he "shifted to the citizen environmental groups that began to sprout up."
Acquisition Information
Gift of Dr. Samuel P. Hays in 1981 and 1984.
Scope and Content Notes
Created by Dr. Samuel P. Hays to support his research interests in United States politics in the 20th century, this collection consists of publications produced by organizations and individuals from both the radical right and radical left of the political spectrum. It includes pamphlets and various types of periodicals such as journals, magazines, newsletters and newspapers, as well as some informational materials on the organizations that published them. Radical movements documented include civil rights, communist and socialist movements, Vietnam War resistance, student activism, countercultural movements, labor, Black power, African politics, right and left economic policies, White supremacy, Christian movements and conservative movements. Also included is one box of subject files containing mostly newspaper clippings and some correspondence.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Previous Citation
Samuel P. Hays Post-World War II Radical Movements Publications Collection, 1915-1982, AIS.1991.18, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Right and left (Political science) -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Radicalism -- United States -- Religious aspects; United States -- Politics and government -- 1945-1989; Radicalism -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Underground press publications -- United Sates; Politics
- Religious Periodicals, 1946-1982; I.
  Scope and Content Notes
  This series consists of periodicals published by various religious groups, predominantly Christian. Most of these publications espouse philosophies closer to the radical right in nature. This series is arranged alphabetically by title of the periodical.
  - Accent on Friends Youth, official publication of the Friends Youth of the Evangelical Friends Alliance (Newberg, OR), v. 1, no. 8, Feb. June, 1966; v. 2, no. 1-9, July 1966-May 1967, 1. (Box 1)
  - Affirm (Milwaukee, WI: Walther Memorial Lutheran Church), v. 1, no. 1-2, March-April 1971, 2.
  - Alarming Cry (Oshkosh, NE), v. 2, no. 1-2, Winter/Spring-Summer/Fall 1955; v. 5, no. 2, Autumn, 1959; v. 12, no. 1, Summer/Autumn, 1966; v. 15, no. 1, Spring/Summer, 1968; v. 16, no. 1, Jan. 1969, 3.
  - Alerte! (Chicago, IL: Advocates of Our Lady), no. 19, 22, 24, 26 28, 30 35, 1959-1965, 4.
  - A.M.E. Zion Quarterly Review (Bedford, PA), v. 79 no. 4, Winter 1967; v. 80 no. 3-4, Fall-Winter 1968; v. 82 no. 1-4, Spring-Winter 1970, 5.
  - American Baptist (Louisville, KY: General Association of Colored Baptists of Kentucky), 1968:no. 29-33, 37-52, July 19-Aug. 16, Sept. 13-Dec. 27; 1969; 1970:no. 1-13, Jan. 2-March 27, 6.
  - Anglo-Saxon World (Ottawa, Ont.: British Israel Association of Greater Vancouver), v. 28, no. 4, 5, 7-11, April, May, July-Dec., 1966; v. 29-31, 1967-1969, 7.
  - Answer: A Christian Journal with the End of Time Message (Rainier, WA: Woodbrook Chapel), v. 2, no. 6-12, June-Dec., 1969; v. 3- 6, no. 4, 1970- June 1973, 8.
  - Ask (Long Prairie, MN: Baptist Bulletin Service), 1967: April/June, Oct./Dec.; 1968: Jan./March, 9.
  - Awake! (Brooklyn, NY: Watchtower Bible and Tract Society of New York, Inc.), v. 48, no. 1, Jan. 8, 1967, 10.
  - Baptist Bible Seminary Bulletin ( Johnson City, NY: Baptist Bible Seminary), v. 28, July, Sept., Dec., 1968; v. 29-32, 1969-1972, 1. (Box 2)
  - Baptist Bible Tribune (Springfield, MO), v. 17, no. 4-20, July-Dec, 1966; v. 18, 1967/1968; v. 19, 1968/1969; v. 20, no. 1-22, June 20–Nov. 8, 1969, 2.
  - Baptist World (Little Rock, AR), v. 1, 1967, 3.
  - Baptist Bulletin (Des Plaines, IA), v. 31, no. 10-12, March-May 1966; v. 32, 1966/1967; v. 33, 1967/1968; v. 34, 1968/1969; v. 35, 1969/1970, 4.
  - Baptist Challenge, a Voice of Independent Baptists (Little Rock, AR), v. 6, June Dec. 1966; v. 7, 1967; v. 8, Jan. Sept., Nov.-Dec. 1968; v. 9, 1969; v. 11, Mar: 1971, 1. (Box 3)
  - Baptist Examiner (Ashland, KY), v. 35, no. 23-27, 37-49, July 16-Aug. 20, 1966, Nov. 5, 1966-Jan. 28, 1967; v. 36 no. 1-31, 33-42, Feb. 4-Sept. 2, Sept. 16-Nov. 18, 1967, 2.
  - Baptist Watchman (Dallas, TX), v. 12, no. 2, Nov. 1966, 3.
  - Bible and the News (Chicago, IL), v. 10 no. 24, Feb. 27, 1954, 4.
  - Bible News Flashes (Minneapolis, MN; Faribault, MN; Galva, IL), v. 7 no. 3, 5, March, May 1946; v. 8, 1947; v. 9 no. 1-9, 11-12, Jan.-Sept., Nov-Dec. 1948; v. 10, 1949; v. 11 no. 1-10, Jan. Oct. 1950; v. 12 no. 1-2, 4-8, 10-12, Jan.-Feb., April-Aug., Oct.-Dec. 1951; v. 13, 1952; v. 14, 1953; v. 15 no. 10-12, Oct.-Dec. 1954; v. 16 no. 2 -5, 7-12, Feb.-May, July-Dec. 1955; v. 17, 1956; v. 18, 1957; v. 19, 1958; v. 20 no. 1-2, Jan.-Feb. 1959, 5.
  - Bible Protestant Messenger (Linwood, NJ), v. 27 no. 2-11, Feb. 1966-Feb. 1967; v. 28 no. 3-10, March 1967-Aug. 1968; v. 29 no. 1-10, Sept. 1968-1969; v. 30 no. 1-10, Aug. 1969-July 1970; v. 31 no. 7-10, Oct. 1970-Sept. 1971; v. 32 no. 1-2, 4-6, Aug. 1971-Dec. 1971, March-Aug. 1972; v. 33 no. 1-6, Sept. 1972- Aug. 1973; v. 34 no. 1-6, Sept. 1973-Fall 1974; v. 35 no. 1-3, Nov./Dec. 1974-April 1975, 6.
  - Bible Protestant Missions News Release (Linwood, NJ), July 1981, 7.
  - Bible Says (Colton, CA: World Prophetic Ministry), April 1967; Jan-March, May-Oct. 1968, 8.
  - Bible Science Newsletter (Caldwell, CO), v. 4 no. 6-12, June-Dec. 1966; v. 5-11, 1967-1973; v. 12 no. 1-7, Jan.-July 1974; v. 13 no. 2, Feb. 1975; v. 18 no. 2, Feb. 1980; v. 19 no. 11-12, Nov.-Dec. 1981; v. 20 no. 1, Jan. 1982, 9.
  - Bible Standard and Herald of Christ's Kingdom (Chester Springs, PA.: Laymen's Home Missionary Movement), v. 46 no. 12, Dec. 1965; v. 47 no. 1, 3, 8-11, Jan, March, Aug.-Nov. 1966; v. 48 no. 2, Feb. 1967; v. 49, no. 2, 11, Feb., Nov. 1968, 1. (Box 4)
  - Blessing Letter (Denver, CO: House of Prayer for All People, Inc.), June-Dec. 1966; 1967-1970; March, May-Sept., Nov.-Dec. 1971; 1972-1976; Jan.-May; Aug.-Dec. 1977; Jan.-Sept., Dec. 1978; 1979; Feb.-Dec. 1980; 1981; Jan.-March 1982, 2.
  - CBA Builder (Wheaton, IL: Conservative Baptist Association of America), 1966-1969; Jan.-April, July/Aug. 1970, 3.
  - Call to Prayer (Tacoma, WA), May/June, Sept./Oct. 1971; March/April 1972, 4.
  - Catacombs (Pittsburgh, PA: Pittsburgh Committee for the Latin Mass), July 1971, 5.
  - Catholic Currents (Washington, DC: Triumph Magazine, Inc.), v. 1 no. 1-2. Dec. 10 1969 Dec. 24 1969; v. 2 no. 1-24, Jan. 21, 1970-Dec. 30, 1970; v. 3 no. 1-13, Jan. 15, 1971-July 15, 1971, 6.
  - Christ for the Nations (Dallas, TX: Christ for the Nations, Inc.), v. 21 no. 5-12, Aug. 1968-March 1969; v. 22 no. 1-12, April 1969-March 1970; v. 23, April 1970-March 1971; v. 24, April 1971-March 1972; v. 25, April 1972-March 1973; v. 26 no. 1-11, April 1973-Feb. 1974; v. 34 no. 10, Jan. 1982, 7.
  - Christian Battle Cry (Englewood, CO), v. 1-3, Oct. 1966- Nov. 1971, 8.
  - Christian Challenge (Bright, Ont.: Brethren of Early Christianity), no. 5, Sept. 1966, 9.
  - Christian Challenge: A Newsletter for Episcopalians (St. Clair Shores, MI: Foundation for Christian Theology), v. 5 no. 5-8, May-Aug. 1966, 10.
  - Christian Cynosure (Chicago, IL: National Christian Association), v. 99 no. 1-12, May 1966-April 1967; v. 100 no. 1-12, 1967-1968; v. 101 no. 1-12, 1968-1969; v. 102 no. 1-12, 1969-1970; v. 103 no. 1-12, 1970-1971; v. 104 no. 1-12, 1971-1972; v. 105 no. 1-12, 1972-1973; v. 106 no. 1-12, 1973-1974; v. 107 no. 1-12, 1974-1975; v. 108, 1975-1976; Autumn-Winter 1976; 1977-1980; Autumn 1981-Spring 1982, 11.
  - Christian Beacon (Collingswood, NJ), v. 29 no. 32, Sept. 17, 1964; v. 43 no. 16, May 25, 1978 (Box 5)
  - Christian Beacon (Collingswood, NJ), v. 29 no. 32, Sept. 17, 1964; v. 43 no. 16, May 25, 1978 (Box 6)
  - Christian Herald: a Voice for the Layman (New York, NY), v. 89, no. 9, Sept. 1966, 1. (Box 7)
  - Christian Heritage (Hackensack, NJ: Christ's Mission), v. 28 no. 6, 8-10, June, Oct- Dec., 1967; v. 29 no. 1 10, 1968; v. 30-38, 1969-1977, 2.
  - Christian Life (Nashville, TN: Christian Life Publications), v. 29 no. 2-12, 1967; v. 30 no. 1, 1968, 3.
  - Christian News ((New Haven, MO: Lutheran News), v. 1, 1968, 4.
  - Christian News (New Haven, MO: Lutheran News), v. 2 no. 1, Jan. 6, 1969; v. 3 no. 31, Aug. 10, 1970, 1. (Box 8)
  - Christian Patriot (Pittsburgh, PA: The Christian Amendment Movement), v. 22 no. 8-11, 1966; v. 23-25, 1967-1969; v. 26 no. 4, 1970, 2.
  - Christian Reporter (Detroit, MI: St. Matthew Christian Walther League, St. Matthew Lutheran Church of the Reformation), 1 issue, undated, 3.
  - Christian Recorder (Nashville, TN: A.M.E.), v. 117 no. 42, 1967; v. 118 no. 50-52, 1968; v. 119 no. 1-47, 1968/1969, 4.
  - Christian Schools Today (Wheaton, IL), 1964-1965, 5.
  - Christian Statesman (Wapello, IA; Pittsburgh, PA: National Reform Association), v. 109 no. 2-6, March-Dec. 1966; v. 110 no. 2-6, March/April-Dec. 1967; v. 111-113, 1968-1970; v. 114 no. 1-2, Jan.-April 1971, 6.
  - Christian Teacher (Wheaton, IL: National Association of Christian Schools), v. 1-8 no. 4, 1964-Sept./Oct. 1971, 7.
  - Christian Vanguard (Hollywood, CA: New Christian Crusade Church), Issue no. 5, Jan. 1972; v. 2 no. 1, Jan. 1973; Issue no. 18, Feb./March 1973; Issue no. 52, April 1976; Issue no. 70, Oct. 1977, 8.
  - Christianity Today (Dayton, OH), v. 8, Oct. 1963-Sept. 1964; v. 9, Oct. 1964-Sept. 1965; v. 10, Nov.-Dec. 1965; v. 11, 1966/1967; v. 12, no. 1-6, 1967, 1. (Box 9)
  - Christopher News Notes (New York, NY: The Christophers), no. 145, 153-201, 203-207, 209, 212-215, 1967-1975, 2.
  - Church School Herald-Journal (Charlotte, NC: Christian Education Dept. of the A.M.E. Zion Church), March-May 1973, 3.
  - Church Times (Oak Hill, WV), v. 22 no. 5/6, 9-12, May/June, Sept.-Dec. 1966; v. 23 no. 1-2, Jan./Feb.-March/Apr 1967; v. 24 no. 1/2, 5-6, Jan./Feb., May-June 1968; v. 25 no. 1-3, Jan.-March 1969; Blue Streak Edition of The Church Times, no. 1, April 1968, 4.
  - Coming Storm (Louisville, KY: Christian Heritage Center), Bulletin no. 29, July 1, 1970, 5.
  - Concern: The Concern of Evangelical Friends for the Fellowship of the Gospel Among all Friends (Newberg, OR: Association of Evangelical Friends), v. 8, 1966, 6.
  - Concerned Presbyterian (Miami, FL), no. 3, Jan. 1966, 7.
  - Confessional Lutheran (Chicago, IL: Confessional Lutheran Publicity Bureau), v. 26 no. 10-12, Oct.-Dec. 1965; v. 27-28, 1966-1968 (not pub. in 1967); v. 29 no. 3, March 1969, 8.
  - Confidential Prayer Letter (Dallas, TX: Christ for the Nations, Inc.), Nov. 1969; Aug.-Sept. 1970; May-June, Aug.-Sept., Nov. 1971; Feb. 1972, 9.
  - Conservative Baptist (Wheaton, IL: Conservative Baptist Agency), v. 1-3 no. 2, Spring 1971-Spring 1973, 10.
  - Conservative Baptist Thrust (Wheaton, IL: Conservative Baptist Agencies), v. 1, no. 1, May/June 1970, 11.
  - Cumberland Flag (Union City, TN), v. 38 no. 3-12, 1967; v. 39 no. 1-4, 8, 10, 1968; v. 40 no. 5, May 15, 1971, 12.
  - Defender of the Christian Faith (Kansas City, MO: Defenders), v. 41 no. 6-12, Oct. 1966-April 1967; v. 42-43, 1967/1968-1968/1969; v. 44 no. 1-2, 4-7, 9-10, May-Aug., Oct. 1969-Jan., March/April 1970; v. 45-48, 1970/1971-1974/1975; v. 49 no. 1, April 1975; v. 50 no. 1-6, 8-12, May-Oct, Dec. 1975-April 1976; v. 51 no. 1-10, 12, May 1976-Feb., April 1977; v. 52 no. 1-3, 5-12, May-July, Sept. 1977-April 1978; v. 53, 1978/1979; v. 54, 1979, 1. (Box 10)
  - Destiny, The Magazine of National Life (Merrimac, MA), v. 37 no. 5, 8 12, 1966; v. 38-40, 1967-1970, 1. (Box 11)
  - Destiny Editorial Letter (Merrimac, MA), v. 40, 1969; v. 41 no. 6, June 1970; v. 42, 1971; v. 43, 1972; v. 44, 1973; v. 45, 1974; v. 46; v. 47, 1975 (lacks June); v. 48 no. 1, 8-12, Jan., Aug.- Dec. 1976; v. 49 no. 1-5, Jan.-April 1977, 2.
  - Dissenter (Latrobe, PA: St. Vincent College Young Americans for Freedom), v. 1, no. 2-3, Jan.-Feb. 1967, 3.
  - Eastern Index (Philadelphia, PA: Christian Methodist Episcopal Church), v. 65 no. 4, May/June 1968, 4.
  - Evangel (Largo, FL: Evangelical Missionary Fellowship), v. 31 no. 8-9, 11, Sept.-Oct., Dec. 1966; v. 32-36 no. 8, 1967-Sept. 1971; v. 36 no. 9-10, Oct.-Nov. 1971; v. 37 no. 11, Dec. 1972; v. 38 no. 6, June 1973; v. 39 no. 3, March 1974; v. 40 no. 5, May 1975, 5.
  - Evangelical Challenge (Bloomsburg, PA), v. 9 no. 2, April/May, 1951; v. 13 no. 1, Feb./March 1956; July/Aug. 1956; March-Aug. 1957; Nov.-Dec. 1958; May-June 1960; Spring 1961, 6.
  - Evangelical Friend (Damascus, OH: Publications Board of Ohio Yearly Meeting of Friends), v. 38 no. 11-12, Nov.-Dec. 1966; v. 39 no. 1-6, Jan.-June 1967, 7.
  - Evangelical Friend (Newberg, OR: Evangelical Friends Alliance), v. 1 1967/1968; v. 2 1968/1969; v. 3 1969/1970; v. 4 1970/1971, 8.
  - Evangelical Methodist (Street, MD: Evangelical Methodist Church and the Fundamental Methodist Church), v. 43 no. 6, 9-12, June, Sept.-Dec. 1965; v. 44, 1966; v. 45, 1967; v. 46, 1968; v. 47, 1969 (lacks Dec.), 9.
  - Exalter (Street, MD), v. 13 no. 1-3, Feb.- Aug. 1966; v. 14 no. 1-3, Feb.-Oct. 1967; v. 15 no. 1-2, April-Nov. 1968; v. 16 no. 1-2, April-Sept. 1969; v. 17, Nov. 1970; v. 18 no. 1, March 1971; v. 19 no. 3, Nov. 1972, 10.
  - Faith for the Family (Greenville, SC: Bob Jones University Press), v. 1 no. 2, May/June 1973, 11.
  - Faith Forward (St. Louis, MO: Evangelical Lutheran synod of Missouri, Ohio, and other States), 1 issue, 1939, 12.
  - Faithful Word (Detroit, MI: State of the Church Conference), v. 1, no. 1-2, 4, 1964; v. 2, no. 1-2, 1965; v. 3, no. 1-3, 1966; v. 4, no. 1-3, 1967; v. 5, no. 1-3, 1968; v. 6, no. 1, 1969, 13.
  - Flag of Truth (Fort Worth, TX), v. 8 no. 5-6, 9-12, May-June, Sept.-Dec., 1966; v. 9 no. 1-2, Jan.-Feb. 1967, 14.
  - Focus on Missions (Cleveland, OH: Fellowship of Missions), v. 11 no. 1, May 1981, 15.
  - Free Methodist (Winona Lake, IN), v. 101 no. 4, 6-24, Feb. 27, March 26-Dec. 17, 1968, 16.
  - Foundation Truth (Lincoln, NE), Sept.-Oct. 1947; March-June, Sept.-Dec. 1949; August 1963; July 1965; Aug., Nov.-Dec. 1966; 1967; Jan.-Sept. 1968, 17.
  - Friends' Intelligencer (Philadelphia, PA: Friends Intelligencer Association), v. 105 no. 28, July 10, 1948, 18.
  - Friends Journal (Philadelphia, PA), v. 15 no. 12, June 15, 1969, 19.
  - Full Life (Los Angeles, CA: American Christian Freedom Society), v. 1 no. 1-7, June-Dec. 1974; v. 2-3, 1975-1976; v. 4 no. 1-2, 4-8, Jan.-Feb., April-Aug. 1977, 20.
  - Fundamentalist: Official voice of the World Baptist Fellowship, v. 22(?) no. 7-8, 10-12, July-Aug., Oct.-Dec. 1966; v. 23(?) 1967; v. 41-54 no. 6, 1968-June 1981; v. 55 no. 1-2, Jan./Feb-March/April 1982, 1. (Box 12)
  - Gentile News (Chicago, IL: Gentile Cooperative Association), v. 1, March 1944-March 1945; v. 2, April 1945-March 1946; v. 3, no. 1-8, 12, April-Nov. 1946, March 1947; v. 4, no. l, April 1947, 2.
  - Glad Tidings (Charlotte, NC), v. 11 no. 9, Sept. 1967, 3.
  - Gospel Truth (Oklahoma City, OK: Southwest Radio Church of the Air), v. 6, no. 11, Oct. 1966, 4.
  - Guardian (Cincinnati, OH: Central Baptist Schools), March/April, Nov./Dec. 1968, 5.
  - Herald of His Coming (Los Angeles, CA), v. 25 no. 8-12, Aug.-Dec. 1966; v. 26-29 no. 8, 1967-Aug. 1970, 6.
  - Highway and Hedge Evangel (Shoals, IN), v. 11 no. 5, May 1963, 7.
  - Hope (Aitken, MN), v. 5 no. 3, 5, May, July 1968, 8.
  - Hope (Hill City, MN), v. 2 no. 6, 10, June, Nov. 1965; v. 3 no. 2-11, Feb.-Dec. 1966; v. 4, 1967, 9.
  - Horizons (Wheaton, IL: Evangelical Alliance Mission), v. 44 no. 5, Sept./Oct. 1968, 10.
  - Humbard Christian Report (Youngstown, OH), v. 7 no. 10-29, March 10-Sept. 8, 1972; v. 8 no. 7-9, 11-16, Feb. 16-March 2, March 16-April 20, 1973, 11.
  - I. H. Convention Herald (Shoals, IN: Inter Denominational Holiness Convention), v. 22 no. 10, Oct. 1966; v. 23 no. 5-12, May-Dec. 1967; v. 24, 1968; v. 25, Jan.-Oct. 1969; v. 26 no. 2, Feb. 1970, 12.
  - Identity (Vancouver, B.C.: Association of Covenant People), v. 32, 1970; v. 33 no. 1, Jan. 1971, 13.
  - Identity (Glendale, CA: Ministry of Christ Church), v. 2, no. 2-6, 1966; v. 3 no. 1-3, 1967; v. 4 no. 1, 3, 1968; v. 5, 1969; v. 6, no. 1-2, 1970, 14.
  - Indian Life and Hope (Rapid City, SD: American Indian Mission), v. 2 no. 3, undated, 15.
  - Interpreter: Announcement Bulletin (Steilacoom, WA: Destiny of America Foundation), v. 25 no. 1-3, Jan./Feb.-Summer/Fall 1964; v. 26 no. 1-2, 4, Summer-Fall, Winter 1965; v. 27 no.1- 4, Summer 1966-Summer 1968, 16.
  - Kingdom Digest (Dallas, TX: Kingdom Bible Institute), v. 23 no. 4, 1962, Aug.; v. 24 no. 4, 7-8, April, July-Aug. 1964; v. 27 no. 8-12, Aug.-Dec. 1966; v. 28, 1967; v. 29, 1968; v. 30 no. 1-2, 5-12, Jan.-Feb., May-Dec., 1969, 1. (Box 13)
  - Landmark Journal (Cincinnati, OH: Landmark Hour), v. 5 no. 4, Sept./Oct., 1966; v. 6 no. 1-4, 9, Jan.-June, Nov. 1967, 2.
  - Liberty (Washington, DC), v. 71 no. 3-v. 73 no. 2, May/June 1976-April 1978, 3.
  - Little Witness From Faith Bible College (Ankeny, IA), v. 3 no. 3, Jan./Feb. 1968, 4.
  - Lutheran News (New Haven, MO: Lutheran News), v. 4 no. 3, Feb. 7, 1966-v. 5 no. 26, Dec. 25, 1967, 5.
  - Lutheran Sentinel (Lake Mills, IA: Evangelical Lutheran Synod), v. 49 no. 3-24, 1966; v. 50 no. 1-23, 1967; v. 51-54, 1968-1972, 6.
  - Lutheran Synod Quarterly (Mankato, MN: Bethany Lutheran Seminary), v. 6, no. 2-4, Dec. 1965-June 1966; v. 7 no. 1-4, Sept. 1966-Aug. 1967; v. 8 no. 1-2, Fall 1967-Winter 1967/1968, 1. (Box 14)
  - Lutherans Alert (Tacollna, WA: Lutherans Alert—National), v. 1 no. 1-v. 7 no. 4, Jan. 1966-April 1972 (lacks v. 4 no. 8, Aug. 1969), 2.
  - Mandate (Lookout, MT), v. 103 no. 1-10, July 1969-April 1970, 3.
  - Message of Old (Bass, AR), v. 4 no. 1, undated; v. 5 no. 1-2, undated; v. 6 no. 3-7, undated, 4.
  - Messenger (Dallas, TX: Congregational Methodist Church), v. 44 no. 37-38, 44-51, Sept. 17-Sept. 24, Nov.5-Dec. 24, 1966; v. 45 no. 1-46, Jan.-Nov 1967, 5.
  - Midnight Cry (Shoals, IN), v. 26 no. 7, July 1965; v. 27 no. 11-12, Nov.-Dec. 1966; v. 28, 1967; v. 29, 1968; v. 30, 1969; v. 32, 1971; v. 33, 1972 (lacks Dec.), 6.
  - Midweek Message (Mobile, AL), v. 22, May 14, 1963; v. 24 no. 9, 11, 43, March 3, March 31, Oct. 19, 1965; v. 25-39, 1966-1979, 7.
  - Militant Truth: a national publication interpreting events from a fundamental Christian and constitutional American viewpoint (Atlanta, GA), v. 21 no. 11, Nov. 1965; v. 22, 1966 (lacks March); v. 23, 1967 (lacks Nov.); v. 24, 1968; v. 25, 1969 (lacks Feb., Nov.); v. 26, 1970 (lacks Oct.); v. 27, 1971(lacks June); v. 28, no. 2-5, Feb.-May 1972; v. 29 no. 12, Dec. 1973; v. 30 no. 1, 3, Jan., March 1974; v. 31 no. 3-4, Sept.-Nov. 1976, 8.
  - Mission of the Messiah (Muskegon, MI), v. 1 no. 6, Dec. 1969, 9.
  - Missionary Baptist Searchlight (Little Rock, AR), v. 28 no. 22-24, Feb. 10-March 10, 1966; v. 29, 1966/1967-1967/1968; v. 30, 1968/1969; v. 31, 1969/1970 (lacks no. 4); v. 32, 1970/1971 (lacks no. 20 21); v. 33, 1971/1972 (lacks no. 19, 22 23), 10.
  - Missionary Herald (Bedford, IN), v. 56 no. 5-7, 9-12, May-July, Sept.-Dec., 1968; v. 57, 1969; v. 58 no. 1-7, Jan.-July, 1970, 11.
  - Missionary Voice of Evangelical Friends (Newburg, OR), v. 12 no. 1, Jan. 1966, 12.
  - National Baptist Union Review (Nashville, TN), v. 73 no. 13-52, 1968; v. 74, 1969; v. 75 no. 1-20, 1970, 1. (Box 15)
  - National Forecast (Topton, NC), no. 247-288, Dec. 1962-Dec. 1966, 1. (Box 16)
  - National Message: Official Journal of the British Israel World Federations (London, England), v. 45, Oct. 12, 1966; v. 46, May-Dec. 1967; v. 47, Jan.-Sept. 1968, 2.
  - Nation's Prayer Call: Official Journal of the National Prayer League Zion Baptist Church (Cincinnati, OH), v. 10, Jan., April/June, 1967; v. 11, July/Sept. 1967; v. 12, Oct./Dec. 1967; v. 13, Jan./March 1968; v. 14, April/June 1968; v. 16, Oct./Dec. 1968; v. 17 no. 1-2, July-Dec. 1971; v. 18 no. 1, Jan./March 1973, 3.
  - Nazarene News (Finleyville, PA), Jan. 1, 1967-April 6, 1969, 4.
  - News in Brief (Merrimac, MA: Destiny Editorial Letter Service), no. 12-19, Dec. 1977-Sept. 1978; no. 24-32, Feb. 1979-Sept. 1980, 5.
  - North American Voice of Fatima (Rockford, IL), v. 3 no. 23, April 25-May 2, 1965, 6.
  - Northwestern Lutheran (Milwaukee, WI: Wisconsin Evangelical Lutheran Synod), v. 53 no. 4-26, 1966; v. 54, 1967; v. 55, 1968; v. 56 no. 1-25, 1969; v. 57 no. 3-4, 1970, 7.
  - Old Fashioned Prophecy (Blackwood, NJ), v. 8-19, 1966-1977, 8.
  - Old Time Gospel Hour News (Lynchburg, VA: Thomas Road Baptist Church), v. 11 no. 11-12, Nov.-Dec. 1972; v. 12 no. 1-7, Jan.-July/Aug.1973, 9.
  - Personal Christianity (Baldwin Park, CA: Personal Christianity Chapel), v. 8 no. 9, Sept. 1968; v. 11 no. 2, Feb. 1971; v. 12, no. 2, 8, Feb., Aug. 1972; v. 16 no. 9, Sept. 1976; v. 17 no. 2-5, 7, 9-11, Feb.-May, July, Sept.-Nov. 1977; v. 18 no. 1-3, Jan.-March 1978; v. 19 no. 3-4, March-April 1979, 10.
  - Point (Cambridge, MA), Dec. 1955-March 1959, 11.
  - Pre Rapture Journal (Auburndale, FL), v. 14 no. 4-10, 12, April-Oct., Dec. 1969; v. 15 no. 1-6, Jan.-July 1970; v. 17, March-Oct. 1972, 12.